

Rohit Tamra

TECHNOLOGY ANALYST

Schaffhauserstrasse 529, 8052 Zurich

engr.rohittamra@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/rohit-tamra-87882b121/

PROFILE

Experienced DevOps Engineer/Site Reliability Engineer with 4.5+ years of background in system analysis and deployments, team leadership, as well as personal administration and professional development. Possess exemplary skills in verbal, written communication and time management. Highly motivated to constantly develop skills and grow professionally.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- DevOps -Docker, Jenkins, GitHub, Nexus, Subversion, Ansible
- Web full stack developer Html, CSS, JavaScript, PHP
- Scripting Shell /Bash Scripting
- Flask Rest Plus Python
- Framework -Ionic 5 with Angular 7, React native
- Programming skills Basics of C, C++, Core Java
- OS Linux

LANGUAGE SKILLS

- English
 - Speak fluently
 - Read and write with proficiency
- German
 - Basic Knowledge
 - Motivated to learn

WORK EXPERIENCE

TECHNOLOGY ANALYST

Infosys June 2021 - Present

- Works for United bank Switzerland (UBS)
- On-site employee

Recommendation Letter Available

SENIOR SYSTEM ENGINEER

Infosys October 2018 - May 2021

• Works for United bank Switzerland (UBS)

Recommendation Letter Available

SYSTEM ENGINEER TRAINEE

Infosys May 2018 - October 2018

Recommendation Letter Available

EDUCATION HISTORY

Tertiary Education

Swami Keshvanand Institute of Technology, Management and Gramothan, Jaipur (RTU, Kota)

 B.Tech. in Computer Science & Engineering with an aggregate of 82.0% (Honours Degree) 2014-2018

Secondary Education

Maheshwari Public School, Ajmer (CBSE)

- Completed higher secondary examination with an aggregate of 78.0%
- Completed senior secondary education with CGPA of 8.8 2012-2014

Other Education

Indian institute of technology Madras

 Advance Certification in Software Engineering for Cloud, Blockchain and IoT 2021-2022

REFERENCE

Mr. Suresh Gurala Senior Consultant , Infosys, UBS - Zurich

T: 0779695454

Email: kumar.suresh2050@gmail.com